Paul K. Perry Papers 2010.0028
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: An Inventory, undated, 1920-1987
  - Notes, memoranda, reports, presentations, photocopies, clippings, articles, surveys, analysis, correspondence, questionnaires, studies, manuscripts, speeches, undated, 1941-2004 (Box 19)
    [Subjects include: Plan for new interviewer organization set-up, Basic framework for the analysis of exploratory attitude research, Concept cards and complexity, Stephan, F.F. POQ, Sampling variance paper, Radiologists sampling experience, Multiple regression analysis, Standard error of median, Deming’s articles Crepsi nonvoter analysis, Mike Kagay materials, Statistical problems, Sampling of human populations, Error projections, Yankelovich prediction of election, poll failure, On the theory of sampling from finite populations, Explanation of Times/CBS polls “Probable electorate,” Sample revisions, Estimate of the Standard error, Assessment of public opinion data sets, Efficacy of times at house as compared with callbacks Mss: Measurement of voting intentions, HEW study materials, Nonvoters, Newsweek, Louis Bean, Research methodology for a national survey of young people aged 13-18, Worksheets.]
  - Publications (serials), undated (Box 20)
  - Research materials, notes, manuscripts, 1936-1974 (Box 21)
    [Subjects include: Bob Dicke, Validity in surveys of voting intentions, Basic factor theory, Elections, New York State Gubernatorial election, I. Crespi m Gallup.]
  - Notes, correspondence, photocopies, studies, papers, reports, clippings, publications, memoranda, 1950s-2004 (Box 22)
    [Subjects include: Plans committee, Binomial sampling, Stock agreement, Precinct results, Redmon, Hayes, stock valuation, by-laws, statement, Crespi, Charlie Roll, Precinct sample, Review and papers for POQ, experimental precincts turnout study, Estimates of civilian population of voting age for states, Obituaries, George Gallup, Jr., Published and mss work of colleagues, Discriminant analysis, Stock and financial correspondence and related materials.]
  - Notes, research, memoranda, procedures, reports, clippings, proceedings, obituaries, reviews, correspondence, publications, 1940s-1990s (Box 23)
    [Subjects include: Voting preferences among voters and nonvoters, Confidence Intervals for clustered samples, Election paper and analysis, Control of the turnout variable, New asymmetric measure of association for ordinal variables, Turnout paper, Standard error of the difference, Computations of r, Computation of 1950 congressional sampling, “Determinants of the outcome of midterm congressional elections,” “Partisanship and performance,” Gallup materials, Relationship between party affiliation and Congressional preference, Party preference and candidate preference, Voters v. nonvoters, Final estimate, Election memoranda, Post Election analysis, Party affiliation by south and nonsouth, Precinct results, Precinct sample, Congressional error survey, Post election research, Congressional question wording comparisons, 1956 election materials, Nonmedical use of psychoactive substances, National and International Systems, Some lessons of forty years of election surveying with the Gallup Poll, Election Survey methods, Survey research and the 1964 election, 1984 presidential election.]
  - Publications (serials), undated (Box 24)
  - Correspondence, memoranda, manuscripts, reprints, clippings, articles, photocopies, notes, press releases, 1939-1987 (Box 25)
    [Subjects include: Precinct sample and turnout scale validation study, Turnout paper, Recollections, Assessment of Public opinion datasets, Materials associated with sale of building, President Nixon, the 1970 senatorial campaign and senate prospects for 1972, Final report on campaign polling in New York, New Jersey attitudes on issues and candidates, Presentation to the American Statistical Association, American Attitudes on race and civil rights, Determinants of the outcome of midterm congressional elections, Simulation of call samples, Detection of interaction effects, AID analysis, Newsweek cover analysis, Companies represented in the Bank of America survey (by city), Television drama audience, Consumer preferences in dress shoe fashions, Rental projection before release, Survey of Business executives ( Bank of America), Presentation record by companies, Political notebook, Survey of reactions to three dimension pictures, wide screen and stereophonic sound, Television audience. RKO/TCF, Nonfiction book Club study, Opinion survey on banking, New York City Motion Picture Market study (RKO), Matrices and mathematical programming (TEMAC), Introductory Calculus I (TEMAC), Assessment of public opinion data sets.]
  - Clippings, notes, articlespapers, reviews, reports, memoranda, surveys, proposals, correspondence and notes, 1939-1997 (Box 26)
    [Subjects include: Presidential Candidate trial heats, Introductory Calculus II (TEMAC), Matrices and mathematical programming (TEMAC), Public Opinion polling on the 1970 election, Congressional, Gallup International Research Institute Conference, Post election analysis, Samples, Attitudes of Western Europeans, Presidential, Turnout, Gallup poll plans for the 1956 presidential election, Clark County opinion survey, Review of current developments in the use of ‘Attitude and activity’ Measures in Consumer market research, Factor analysis, Crespi papers, Bayes, Multivariate analysis, Path analysis, Deming, Intelligence tests.]
  - Notes, correspondence, directory, clippings, precinct reports, publications, undated, 1948-1984 (Box 27)
    [Subjects include: Psychographic, Votes, Public opinion studies in the United States, Gallup poll plans for the 1956 presidential election, Election Surveys and the British election, Presidential popularity ratings from Eisenhower to Reagan, RAI schedule of rates and services.]
  - Books, clippings, correspondence, ephemera, manuscript, notes, publications, 1937, 1945-1949, 1954, 1978-1980, 1987; 1.0 Linear feet Folders with tabs/labels; books (Box 28)
    [Subjects include: Atlantic Monthly, Audience Research Inc., Computation of Descriptive Statistics- Jack W. Dunlap, European Society for Opinion and Marketing Research, Dr. George H. Gallup, Increasing Profits with Continuous Audience Research, Institute for Social Research at the University of Michigan, The Joint Center for Political Studies, Montgomery Advertiser, Public Opinion Reporters.]